The kids aren't alright.
Clown is a horror, thriller film directed by Jon Watts.
A loving father finds a clown suit for his son's birthday party, only to realize the
suit is part of an evil curse that turns its wearer into a killer.
Kent, played by Andy Powers.
Meg, played by Laura Allen.
Karlsson, played by Peter Stormare.
Jack, played by Christian Distefano.
Walt, played by Chuck Shamata.
Denise, played by Elizabeth Whitmere.
Clown is a 2014 American supernatural horror film directed by Jon Watts in his feature directorial debut,
produced by Mac Cappuccino, Eli Roth, and Cody Ryder, and written by Watts and Christopher Ford.
It stars Eli Roth, Laura Allen, Andy Powers, and Peter Stormare.
Visual effects for the clown monster were done by Jagdeep
Khoza, Alterian, Inc., and Tony Gardner.
Principal photography began in November 2012, in Ottawa.
The film was released in Italy on November 13, 2014, in the United Kingdom on March 2,
2015, and in the United States on June 17, 2016, by Dimension Films.
The film received mixed reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of child murder, dark
comedy, clown, murder, killer clown.
The tone is dark and intense.